Office of the President Jill Ker Conway Files, 1974-1985
Smith College Archives
- SERIES V. ADMINISTRATIVE OFFICES
  - Treasurer
    - -President's Discretionary Fund
      - -Supporting Material 1982-1985 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - -Reports
      - -General 1976-1980 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - -General 1981-1985 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - -"Analysis of Student Aid Support from Smith Clubs" 1975 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - -"Money Management and Short Term Investments" 1975 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - -Student ID Numbers 1975 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - -Treasurer Search 1984 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Vocational Office (Box 46)
    See Series V. Administrative Offices-Career Development Office
- SERIES VI. ALUMNAE
  This series includes material on a number of issues related to the alumnae, as well as the Alumnae Association and its activities. The bulk of the files contain information about the Alumnae Association, class reunions, Smith Clubs, and specific individuals. The section related to individuals is in alphabetical order, and contains correspondence to, from and about alumnae. Many are routine and pro forma letters of thank you for attending certain functions, or congratulations on administrative successes. However, there are also letters scattered throughout addressing specific issues pertinent to the period. There is also a file of birthday greetings sent to alumnae by the President's Office, generally offering congratulations on reaching a remarkably advanced age.
  Information about alumnae involvement with Admissions can be found in the records of Alumnae/Admissions Task Force in the Committees and Boards series, and in the records of the Admissions Office's Candidates Committees in the Administrative Offices series.
  - Alumnae Association (Box 1)
    - -General 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - -General 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - -Alumnae Biography Project 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - -Alumnae Biography Project 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - -Alumnae Biography Project 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - -Alumnae College
      - -General 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - -Alumnae College of the Rockies 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - -Alumnae Council 1976-1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - -Alumnae Fellows Program 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - -Alumnae Gym (Box 1)
      See Series VII. Buildings & Grounds-Alumnae Gym-Smith Alumnae Committee to Save the Alumnae Gym
    - -Alumnae Lecture Fund 1975-1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - -Alumnae Seminars 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - -Athletics Slide Show 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - -Centennial Celebration 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - -Centennial Panels (Box 2)
      - -General 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - -Chicago 1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - -Cleveland 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - -Greenwich, CT 1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - -Houston 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - -Los Angeles 1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - -Minneapolis 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - -Northampton 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - -St. Louis 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - -San Francisco 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - -Washington, D.C. 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - -Westchester 1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - -Faculty Speaking Tours 1976-1984 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - -Minority Alumnae
      - -General 1976, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - -Black Alumnae Directory 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - -Black Alumnae Weekend 1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - -Nominating Committee 1976-1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - -Seven College Conference 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - -Smith Alumnae Quarterly 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - -Smith Alumnae Quarterly 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - -Smith Resources Program 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - -Travel/Tours
      - -Australia 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - -China 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - -Copenhagen 1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - -London 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - -Middle East 1977-1978, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - -Workshops
      - -Challenges, Choices, & Change 1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - -Microcomputers 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - -Retirement Planning 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - -Tropism & Refraction 1975-1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - -Young Alumnae Conference 1975-1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Alumnae Fund
    - -General 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - -General 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - -General 1981-1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - -Sophia Smith Associates 1975-1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Candidates Committees (Box 4)
    See Series V. Administrative Offices-Admissions-Alumnae Candidates Committees
  - Class of 1950 Research Project 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Feminist & Lesbian Alumnae of Smith College [FLASC] (Box 4)
    See Series IV. Administrative Issues-Lesbianism-Feminist & Lesbian Alumnae of Smith College
  - Ginling College 1979-1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Individuals
    - -Birthdays 1975-1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - -A ca. 1975-1985 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - -Bel Geddes, Anne 1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - -Ba-Bi ca. 1975-1985 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - -Bo-Bz ca. 1975-1985 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - -Boyden, Kathleen 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - -Bush, Barbara 1980-1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - -Butler, Jessica Haver 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - -C ca. 1975-1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - -D-E ca. 1975-1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - -F-G ca. 1975-1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - -H ca. 1975-1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - -Harlan, Ann 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - -I-K ca. 1975-1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - -L ca. 1975-1985 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - -Ma-Me ca. 1975-1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - -Mi-Mz ca. 1975-1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - -N-O ca. 1975-1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - -P-Q ca. 1975-1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - -R ca. 1975-1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - -Reagan, Nancy 1980-1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - -Reagan, Nancy 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - -Sa-Sm ca. 1975-1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - -Smith, Grace Kellog 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - -Sn-Sz ca. 1975-1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - -Snyder, Margaret Hepburn 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - -T-V ca. 1975-1985 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - -Thomas, Caroline Bedell 1977-1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - -W-Z ca. 1975-1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Reunions
    See also Series XI. Events-Commencement
    - -1976 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - -1977 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - -1978 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - -1979 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - -1980 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - -1981 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - -1982 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - -1983 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - -1984 1984 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - -1985 1985 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - -Questionnaires 1978-1984 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - School for Social Work 1978, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Smith Alumnae for Alternatives 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Smith Clubs (Box 8)
    - -General 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - -General 1977-1985 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - -Open Minds Open Doors Panels
      - -General 1984 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - -Chicago 1984 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - -Dallas 1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - -Kansas City 1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - -Miami 1984 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - -Phoenix 1984 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - -Arizona 1976-1985 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - -California 1975-1984 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - -Colorado 1976-1981 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - -Connecticut 1975-1984 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - -Delaware 1975 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - -Florida 1975-1984 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - -Georgia 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - -Hawaii 1976 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - -Illinois 1975-1984 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - -Louisiana 1977 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - -Massachusetts 1974-1985 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - -Minnesota 1976, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - -Missouri 1976, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - -New Hampshire 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - -New Jersey 1976-1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - -New York
      - -General 1976-1985 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - -New York City 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - -New York City 1978-1984 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - -Long Island 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - -Westchester 1975-1984 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - -North Carolina 1975-1976, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - -Ohio 1976-1985 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - -Oregon 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - -Pennsylvania 1975-1985 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - -Rhode Island 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - -Texas 1975-1981 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - -Vermont 1977 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - -Washington, D.C./Baltimore 1975-1985 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - -Wisconsin 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - -Australia 1983 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - -Canada 1976-1983 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - -Europe 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - -Japan 1975, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Students' Aid Society 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- SERIES VII. BUILDINGS & GROUNDS
  Student residences are grouped together and organized alphabetically.
  This series includes records related to the maintenance and development of campus structures and infrastructure. Construction projects during Conway's term included the Friedman Apartments, Ainsworth Gym, and indoor and outdoor track and tennis facilities. Major renovations were completed for Drew Hall, Lyman Plant House, Neilson Library and the Alumnae Gym.
  Related material may be found in the Committees and Boards series in the records of the Campus Planning Committee, Facilities Planning Committee, Committee on Faculty Offices, Grounds Committee, Ad-hoc Committee for the Selection of Architects and Supervision of Building Programs, Committee on Space Allocation, and the Campus Beautification Committee. There is additional information in the Administrative Offices series in the records of the Physical Plant as well as the Assistant to the President for Campus Planning (President's Office).
  - General (Box 1)
    - -Access for the Disabled 1976-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      See also Series V. Admin Offices-Institutional Research (MAR-APR 1984)
    - -Campus Signage 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - -Parking and Traffic 1976-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - -Parking and Traffic 1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - -Parking and Traffic 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alumnae Gym 1976-1983 (Box 1)
    - -General 1976-1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - -Smith Alumnae Committee to Save Alumnae Gym 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - -Smith Alumnae Committee to Save Alumnae Gym 1977-1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Athletic Facilities
    - -General 1976-1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - -Ainsworth Gym 1976-1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - -Athletic Facility Study Feb 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - -Athletic Fields and Tennis Courts 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - -Indoor Track 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - -Riding Facilities 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - -Scott Gym 1976-1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bass Hall (Box 2)
    See Series VII. Buildings & Grounds-Clark Science Center-Addition
  - Botanic Garden
    See also Series IX. Committees & Boards-Grounds Committee
    - -Annual Reports 1975-1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - -General 1975-1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - -General 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - -Green World Summer Program (Box 2)
      See Series XI. Events-Summer Programs
    - -Lyman Plant House 1976-1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Clark Science Center
    - -General 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - -Addition 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - -Space Utilization Report Oct 1981 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - College Hall 1976-1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Davis Student Center 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Drew Hall 1976-1984 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Club (Box 2)
    See Series XII. Faculty & Staff-Faculty Club
  - Fine Arts Center 1976-1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Garrison Hall 1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Hills Chapel 1979 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - John M.Greene Hall 1981 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Juniper Lodge 1975-1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Mendenhall Center for the Performing Arts 1976-1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    See also Series II. Academic Departments-Theatre & Speech
  - Mill River
    See Series VII. Buildings & Grounds-Paradise Pond
    - Neilson Library 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Neilson Library 1978-1985, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Paradise Pond 1981-1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - President's House
      See also Series XI. Events-President's House Events
      - -General 1975-1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - -Personnel 1975-1985, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Sage Hall 1976 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Seelye Hall 1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Stoddard Hall 1975-1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Stoddard Hall 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Student Residences
      - -General 1976-1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
        - -Cooperative Living 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
          See also Series VII. Buildings & Grounds-Student Residences-Hover House, Tenney House, and Friedman House
        - -New York Times Delivery 1977-1981 (Box 3, Folder 14)
        - -Renovations 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - -Cutter-Ziskind Houses 1976-1983 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - -Dawes House 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - -Friedman Apartments 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - -Friedman Apartments 1977-1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - -Hampshire House 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - -Hopkins House 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - -Hover House 1975-1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - -Magna House (Box 4)
        See Series IV. Administrative Issues-Clarke School for the Deaf-Magna House
      - -Oak House 1979-1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
        See also Series V. Administrative Offices-Dean of Students
      - -Parsons Annex (Box 4)
        See Series VII. Buildings & Grnds-Stud Res-Hover House
      - -Siipola House (Box 4)
        See Series VII. Buildings & Grounds-Garrison Hall
      - -Tenney House 1975-1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - -Washburn House 1976-1985 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Wright Hall 1978-1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- SERIES VIII. COLLEGES AND UNIVERSITIES
  The files are organized alphabetically by institution, with a series of alphabetical miscellaneous material at the end.
  This series consists of correspondence, reports and newspaper clippings from other institutions regarding cooperative programs, institutional activities and events, as well as common educational issues.
  For institutions of either the Five Colleges, Seven Sisters or Twelve College Exchange, see also the Intercollegiate Associations series.
  - Amherst College (Box 1)
    - -General 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - -General 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - -Faculty Compensation Study 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Barnard College 1976-1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Brown University 1977-1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bryn Mawr College 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bryn Mawr College 1979-1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Colby College 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Cornell University 1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Dartmouth College 1977-1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Doshisha University (Box 1)
    See Series III. Academic Programs-Student Exchange with Japan
  - Duke University 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Fudan University (Box 1)
    See Series III. Academic Programs-Student Exchange with China
  - Ginling College (Box 1)
    See Colleges and Universities-Nanking Teachers College -and- Series VI. Alumnae-Alumnae Association-Travel/Trips-China -and- Series VI. Alumnae-Ginling College
  - Hampshire College 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Hampshire College 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Hampshire College 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Harvard University (Box 2)
    - -General 1979-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - -Institute for Educational Management 1977-1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology
    - -General 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - -Sloan Foundation Seminars 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts, University of 1976-1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Michigan, University of 1977-1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Middlebury College 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Mills College 1975-1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Mount Holyoke College
    - -General 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - -General 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - -General 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - -International Internships 1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - -Sesquicentennial Symposium 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - -Smith-Mt. Holyoke Institute for Research on Women's Experience and Public Policy 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Nanking Teachers College 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - New Hampshire, University of 1978-1985 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Northeastern University 1976-1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Oberlin College 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Oxford University 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Princeton University 1977-1983 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Radcliffe College 1976-1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Rochester, University of 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Sarah Lawrence College 1981-1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Spelman College 1978-1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Sydney, University of 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Tulane University 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Vassar College 1975-1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Wellesley College 1975-1980 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Wellesley College 1981-1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Wesleyan University 1976-1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Wheaton College 1975-1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Williams College 1976-1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Yale University 1978-1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous
    - -A-C 1975-1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - -D-M 1975-1985 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - -N-S 1975-1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - -T-Z 1975-1985 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- SERIES IX. COMMITTEES AND BOARDS
  However, college policy and the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act require the restriction of the records of both the Board of Trustees and the Board of Counselors.
  This series includes correspondence, reports and working papers of the standing and ad-hoc committees and boards of the college. The most central and far-reaching decision-making bodies are the Board of Trustees, the Board of Counselors, and the Committee on Planning and Resources (previously the College Planning Committee and the Faculty Planning Committee). Other significant committees in this series include several faculty committees, the Committee on Social Responsibility and the Committee on Student Affairs. Also included in this series are three free-standing administrative groups: Administrative Department Heads, Senior Administrative Group, and Senior Staff. The files of the Senior Staff are the most extensive of these three groups. The Senior Staff (also know as the President's Staff) included key administrative figures, such as the Treasurer, the Directors of Development and Public Relations, Assistants to the President, and Deans and Associate Deans. Minutes and major reports from most committees are available in the Dean of the Faculty Records of the Smith College Archives.
  - General 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - General 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Academic Computing, Committee on 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Academic Computing, Committee on 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Academic Honor Board (Box 1)
    See Series XVII. Students-Organizations-Academic Honor Bd.
  - Academic Policy, Committee on
    - -General 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - -General 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - -Subcommittee on Curricular Review 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - -Subcommittee on Curricular Review 1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - -Subcommittee on Curricular Review 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Administrative Information Systems Policy Committee 1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Administrative Information Systems Policy Committee 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Administrative Board 1976-1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Administrative and Clerical Personnel Policy Boards 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Administrative and Clerical Personnel Policy Boards 1978-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Department Heads 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Staff Grievance Committee 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Admission, Board of 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Admission, Board of 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Admission, Board of 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Athletics, Committee on 1981-1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Afro-American Studies Advisory Committee
    - -General 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - -Final Report Jun 1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Aid to Faculty Scholarship, Committee on 1977-1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    See also Series IX. Cttes & Bds-Faculty Compensation and Development
  - Alcohol Task Force 1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Alumnae/Admissions Task Force 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Appointment and Re-appointment Procedures, Ad-hoc Committee on 1977 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Architects & Supervision of Building Programs, Ad-hoc Committee for the Selection of 1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Bookstore Advisory Committee 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Campus Beautification Committee 1985 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Campus Computing Committee 1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Campus Planning Committee 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Child Study Committee 1980-1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Weekend, Committee on 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Clerical Staff Grievance Committee 1977-1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - College Planning and Resources, Committee on 1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - College Planning and Resources, Committee on 1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - College Planning and Resources, Committee on Jan-Oct 1977 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - College Planning and Resources, Committee on Nov-Dec 1977 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - College Planning and Resources, Committee on 1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - College Planning and Resources, Committee on 1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - College Planning and Resources, Committee on 1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - College Planning and Resources, Committee on 1981 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - College Planning and Resources, Committee on Jan-Mar 1982 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - College Planning and Resources, Committee on Apr-Oct 1982 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - College Planning and Resources, Committee on Nov-Dec 1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - College Planning and Resources, Committee on Jan-Jul 1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - College Planning and Resources, Committee on Aug-Dec 1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - College Planning and Resources, Committee on 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Committees, Committee on 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Committees, Committee on 1977 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Committees, Committee on Jan-Mar 1978 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Committees, Committee on Apr-Dec 1978 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Committees, Committee on 1979-1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Communications and Record-Keeping Study Group (Box 5)
    - -General 1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - -Administrative Data Processing 1979 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - -Admissions Office 1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - -Assistant to the President for Campus Planning 1979 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - -Career Development Office 1979 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - -Chapel 1979 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - -Dean of the College, Office of the 1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - -Deferred Gifts and Bequests, Committee on 1979 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - -Development Office 1979 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - -Financial Aid Office 1979 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - -Graduate Study Office 1979 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - -Health Services 1979 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - -Library 1979 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - -Personnel Services 1979 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - -Physical Plant 1979 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - -President and Board of Trustees, Offices of 1979 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - -Registrar's Office 1979 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - -Secretary of the College, Office of 1979 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Community Policy, Committee on 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Conference Committee 1975-1983 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Course Critique, Committee on 1976-1984 (Box 5, Folder 21)